Uncle
Come by again when you're free
Take these home to eat
Such big forest frogs are worth a lot of money
You should take them back
Daniel
These forest frogs are almost ready for market
Why buy back these defects now
Believe it or not
I can turn trash into treasure
Turn stone to gold
Brother-in-law
These forest frogs aren't even that big
You should give good ones as gifts
Jason
Go catch some big ones from my farm
Show them off to everyone
Brother-in-law
You probably don't know this
Jason cracked your secret formula
See these inferior ones
After eating the secret feed
They grow four grams a day
Impossible
I know what Jason is capable of
Unless
Something else was added to this feed
What do you know
This is a tech upgrade
Works much better than yours
You just see I developed better feed
And got jealous
So you're slandering me
Lewes
Stop trying to sow discord
I saw the feed's effects myself
Look
After only ten days of feeding
They've already caught up to your forest frogs
Your skills
Are nothing special
Lewes
If you had just given me a raise
Your frogs would be twice as big now
You wouldn't have lost Walter's multi-million order
Too bad you failed to recognize my talent
Now I'm giving all this to Daniel
I will make you regret your decision
These frogs
Don't look right
This batch of frogs
Will definitely have problems